https://www.precisionsharp.com/shipping-returns-privacy/

Colin Taylor
G Series (German Line)
J Series - Convex
JFB SERIES - CONVEX
True Lefty
Patriot (Made in USA)
Site Information
Loading... Please wait...
Colin Taylor
G Series (German Line)
J Series - Convex
JFB SERIES - CONVEX
True Lefty
Patriot (Made in USA)
Shipping/Returns/Privacy
120 Fourth Street, Mount Wolf, PA 17347717.266.7348   info@precisionsharp.com
Returns Policy
You may return most new, unopened items within 30 days of delivery for a full refund, excluding shipping. We'll also pay the return shipping costs if the return is a result of our error (you received an incorrect or defective item, etc.).You should expect to receive your refund within four weeks of giving your package to the return shipper, however, in many cases you will receive a refund more quickly. This time period includes the transit time for us to receive your return from the shipper (5 to 10 business days), the time it takes us to process your return once we receive it (3 to 5 business days), and the time it takes your bank to process our refund request (5 to 10 business days).If you need to return an item, simply login to your account, view the order using the "Complete Orders" link under the My Account menu and click the Return Item(s) button. We'll notify you via e-mail of your refund once we've received and processed the returned item.  If you need to return a product purchased at a trade show, phone order or by other means, please call us 717.266.7348 so we can make a record of the situation and return to us with a copy of your detailed sales receipt or invoice.  Clipper blades cannot be returned.  For warranty information on items other than scissors, check with the manufacturer and return directly to them.Shipping
We can ship to virtually any address in the world. Note that there are restrictions on some products, and some products cannot be shipped to international destinations.
When you place an order, we will estimate shipping and delivery dates for you based on the availability of your items and the shipping options you choose.  Most orders are shipped within 2 business days of receipt, pending national grooming and dog show schedules. Estimated delivery is generally within 3 to 5 business days, pending time of year, weather conditions and other unforeseen events which could impact delivery times. Depending on the shipping provider, shipping date estimates may or may not appear on the shipping quotes page. Please note that every shear is quality checked and receive a specialized, custom edge by Randy Lowe, our master sharpener before shipment.
Please also note that the shipping rates for many items we sell are weight-based. The weight of any such item can be found on its detail page. To reflect the policies of the shipping companies we use, all weights will be rounded up to the next full pound.
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.precisionsharp.com.  This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 717-266-7348 or via email (cheryl@precisionsharp.com).
To edit this page simply login to the control panel, click the Website Content tab and choose the View Web Pages option. Click Edit next to the Shipping & Returns page and you can change this text. A sample returns policy is shown below which you can edit as needed.
Sign up for our newsletter
Name
Email
Quick Links
About Us
Curve vs Ultimate Super Curve
Custom Shears & Blades
Services
G Series (German Line)
J Series - Convex
JFB SERIES - CONVEX
True Lefty
Patriot (Made in USA)
